Let me go! I’m not going. Let go!
دعني أذهب! لن أذهب. دعني أذهب!
Let me go right now! I didn't do it.
دعوني أذهب الآن! لم أفعل ذلك.
I told you, I didn't do it!
قلت لك، لم أفعل ذلك!
Let go!
اتركه!
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Hold on.
يتمسك.
Let go of me this instant!
اتركني الآن!
I didn't do it, everyone!
لم أفعل ذلك يا جماعة!
It was Ranya. Ranya did it all by herself!
كانت رانيا. رانيا فعلت كل شيء بمفردها!
She already confessed that she did it alone!
لقد اعترفت بالفعل بأنها فعلت ذلك بمفردها!
I didn't do anything at all, I swear!
أقسم أنني لم أفعل أي شيء على الإطلاق!
Everyone, I am so truly sorry.
أيها الناس، أنا آسف حقاً.
I know what happened was wrong.
أعلم أن ما حدث كان خطأً.
I apologize.
أنا أعتذر.
I made a mistake, can you all please forgive me?
لقد ارتكبت خطأً، هل يمكنكم جميعاً أن تسامحوني؟
I am so, so sorry!
أنا آسف جداً جداً!
It was Ranya... Ranya did it all on her own!
كانت رانيا... رانيا فعلت كل ذلك بمفردها!
I didn't do a thing.
لم أفعل شيئاً.
I am truly sorry to everyone.
أنا آسف حقاً للجميع.
I’m sorry... I’m so sorry.
أنا آسف... أنا آسف جداً.
I didn't do it. I didn't do it!
لم أفعل ذلك. لم أفعل ذلك!
Mom... did you never even love me?
أمي... ألم تحبيني أبداً؟
You’re just stupid!
أنت غبي!
You’ve ruined everything.
لقد أفسدت كل شيء.
Why should I even bother being nice to you, huh?
لماذا عليّ أن أكلف نفسي عناء أن أكون لطيفاً معك، هاه؟
The only reason I ever raised you was for this company!
السبب الوحيد الذي دفعني لتربيتك هو هذه الشركة!
I have evidence that Ranya had nothing to do with this.
لدي أدلة تثبت أن رانيا لم يكن لها أي علاقة بهذا الأمر.
I’d like to speak with Ranya for a moment, please.
أود التحدث مع رانيا للحظة، من فضلك.
But Pimchat... I didn’t do it!
لكن بيمشات... لم أفعل ذلك!
I loved Khun Wichai so much,
أحببتُ خون ويتشاي كثيراً،
how could I ever do something like that?
كيف لي أن أفعل شيئاً كهذا؟
Don't you remember the funeral?
ألا تتذكر الجنازة؟
I was devastated.
لقد شعرتُ بالانهيار.
I didn't do it!
لم أفعل ذلك!
Ran, why are you taking the fall for her?
ران، لماذا تتحمل أنت المسؤولية عنها؟
Don't you see?
ألا ترى؟
She doesn’t love you the way you love her.
إنها لا تحبك بالطريقة التي تحبها بها.
I’m sorry...
أنا آسف...
It’s all my fault.
كل هذا خطأي.
It’s okay.
لا بأس.
You can let her go now, Ran.
يمكنك تركها تذهب الآن يا ران.
It’s my fault.
هذا خطأي.
I was so stupid.
كنت غبياً جداً.
Stop blaming yourself.
توقف عن لوم نفسك.
You're my brave girl.
أنتِ فتاتي الشجاعة.
From now on, no matter what happens,
من الآن فصاعدًا، مهما حدث،
don’t run away again, okay?
لا تهرب مرة أخرى، حسناً؟
We’re going to fight this together.
سنخوض هذه المعركة معاً.
Can you promise me that?
هل يمكنك أن تعدني بذلك؟
K’Wichai’s death wasn't an accident after all.
لم يكن موت كويتشاي حادثاً في نهاية المطاف.
The medicine was swapped by K’Jintana.
تم استبدال الدواء بواسطة كي جينتانا.
This was a murder.
كانت هذه جريمة قتل.
If it's about the work plan, I’m not mad at you at all.
إذا كان الأمر يتعلق بخطة العمل، فأنا لست غاضباً منك على الإطلاق.
In fact, I’m the one who should apologize.
في الحقيقة، أنا من يجب أن يعتذر.
You’ve done so much for me,
لقد فعلت الكثير من أجلي،
yet I still failed to trust you.
ومع ذلك، ما زلتُ عاجزاً عن الوثوق بك.
I understand.
أفهم.
Honestly, I was just more afraid that you’d be mad.
بصراحة، كنت أخشى أكثر أن تغضب.
Is something wrong?
هل هناك خطب ما؟
Nothing,
لا شئ،
Eat up.
تناول الطعام.
The cause of K’Wichai’s death wasn't an accident.
لم يكن سبب وفاة كويتشاي حادثًا.
My mother was the one who planned the whole thing.
كانت والدتي هي من خططت لكل شيء.
Why did Jintana have to kill you?
لماذا اضطرت جينتانا لقتلك؟
Dad, I can’t even look at Ranya’s face anymore.
يا أبي، لم أعد أستطيع حتى النظر إلى وجه رانيا.
P'Chat,
بي شات،
may I come in?
هل لي بالدخول؟
...Fine, that’s okay.
...حسناً، لا بأس.
I’ll wait for you right here.
سأنتظرك هنا.
I'll wait until you’re ready to talk to me.
سأنتظر حتى تكون مستعدًا للتحدث معي.
I understand...
أفهم...
Everyone loves their own father.
كل شخص يحب والده.
I have no excuses at all.
ليس لدي أي أعذار على الإطلاق.
I am truly sorry.
أنا آسف حقاً.
I’m so sorry for what my mother did.
أنا آسف جداً لما فعلته والدتي.
Chat loves Dad very much...
تشات يحب والده كثيراً...
but I love you very much too, Ranya.
لكنني أحبك كثيراً أيضاً يا رانيا.
Dad isn't upset with me, is he?
أبي ليس غاضباً مني، أليس كذلك؟
I know you didn't do anything wrong.
أعلم أنك لم تفعل أي شيء خاطئ.
But I still just can't bring myself to fully trust you yet.
لكنني ما زلت لا أستطيع أن أثق بك تماماً حتى الآن.
It’s okay.
لا بأس.
I understand.
أفهم.
Even though you helped me with everything,
على الرغم من أنك ساعدتني في كل شيء،
I still...
ما زلت...
If it were me,
لو كنت مكاني،
I probably would have lost it way more than you did.
ربما كنت سأفقد أعصابي أكثر بكثير مما فعلت أنت.
You’ve been so strong.
لقد كنتِ قوية للغاية.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
let’s do it together to make things right.
فلنعمل معاً على إصلاح الأمور.
We’ll get through this together, okay?
سنتجاوز هذا معًا، حسنًا؟
Thank you for giving me a chance.
شكراً لإتاحة هذه الفرصة لي.
It's a chance for both of us.
إنها فرصة لنا نحن الاثنين.
K’Pimprapha, K’Wichai...
K'Pimprapha, K'Wichai...
After this,
بعد ذلك،
I will take care of P'Chat as best as I possibly can.
سأعتني بـ P'Chat بأفضل ما أستطيع.
And I’ll take care of her, too.
وسأعتني بها أيضاً.
As long as I has her here in the company, I’m not afraid of anything anymore.
طالما أنها موجودة هنا في الشركة، فلن أخشى أي شيء بعد الآن.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I love you the most.
أحبك أكثر من أي شيء.
I love you too, Ranya.
وأنا أحبك أيضاً يا رانيا.